[
    {
        "question": "How many Countries in South America?",
        "answers": [
            10,
            12,
            14,
            16
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "How many languages are officially spoken in North America?",
        "answers": [
            3,
            4,
            6,
            7
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "How many official languages in the world?",
        "answers": [
            103,
            114,
            128,
            140
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "How many countries are there?",
        "answers": [
            200,
            250,
            280,
            310
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "How many countries in Europe?",
        "answers": [
            39,
            50,
            53,
            55
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "How many countries in Asia?",
        "answers": [
            52,
            60,
            70,
            75
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "How many countries in the Antarctica?",
        "answers": [
            4,
            5,
            6,
            7
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the code phone number of the French Southern Territories in the Antarctica ;)?",
        "answers": [
            212,
            262,
            314,
            147
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the official language of Angola?",
        "answers": [
            "French",
            "English",
            "Portuguese",
            "Spanish"
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the official languages of Djibouti?",
        "answers": [
            "French and English",
            "French and Arabic",
            "Portuguese and Arabic",
            "Spanish and French"
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    }
]